<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on Luke Brunning</title>
    <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on Luke Brunning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Tools are Not Toys</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-03-08-your-tools-are-not-toys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-03-08-your-tools-are-not-toys/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately my beloved TextExpander has recently stopped working in ConEmu. Ironically this coincided with the update notes proudly declaring that expansion was now working in ConEmu! Those nice people at Smile are helping me get to the bottom of it, but in the mean time I decided to look around at the options in the console world in Windows. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to take long.
I opened up the PowerShell ISE; I&amp;rsquo;ve never really used it, preferring Sublime Text (I&amp;rsquo;ve also been flirting with Visual Studio Code) but I grabbed a Solarized theme and thought it may be fun to the &amp;lsquo;Intellisense&amp;rsquo; available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday is the new Monday</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-05-sunday-is-the-new-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-05-sunday-is-the-new-monday/</guid>
      <description>Being an Englishman in New Technology, I&amp;rsquo;m rather used to changing regional settings. As a former serial Linux experimenter it almost became a reflex action I never even thought about. I was always puzzled by the notion of Sunday as the first day of the week, however as I sit here on a Sunday morning doing my GTD weekly review and looking at the week ahead in my calendar it suddenly occurred to me that if I set Sunday as the first day, then when I look at the weekly view in the calendar then I won&amp;rsquo;t have to move it forward a week.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>