<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
        <title>Luke Brunning</title>
        <description>Luke Brunning - Luke Brunning</description>
        <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk</link>
        <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk</link>
        <lastBuildDate>2015-06-21T14:48:14+01:00</lastBuildDate>
        <pubDate>2015-06-21T14:48:14+01:00</pubDate>
        <ttl>1800</ttl>


        <item>
                <title>Garden Upgrade LIVE</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;My garden project is now fully underway! After weeks of trying to find someone to actually work on this project I finally found just the right person. We decided it was best that I project manage the whole thing and he just supply labour as I wanted to specify most of the materials. This has worked out really well. He&#39;s advised me when I needed it and come up with some good ideas of areas which I wasn&#39;t sure about. For example, the aggregate used to level off the surface before paving needs an edge to hold it in. Someone else had avised a paving slab embedded vertically which would have worked but not looked great and also been a relatively expensive solution. Andy suggested using fencing gravel boards, which not only look better, but were a cheaper solution. In looking for these &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.garden-fence-panels.co.uk/concrete-posts-bases/concrete-base-panel-rock-face.html&quot;&gt;gravel boards&lt;/a&gt; I also found aggregate at a cheaper price than other places I had been looking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy and his son came to get the decking up to scope out Phase 2 laying the groundworks and did a super fast job as you can see from the movie here;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/130202556&quot; width=&quot;500&quot; height=&quot;375&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/130202556&quot;&gt;phase01 a&lt;/a&gt; from &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/lukebrunning&quot;&gt;Luke Brunning&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com&quot;&gt;Vimeo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve now revised my plans and decided to drop the decking area and going with just a paving and turfed area. I’m hoping the summer house and furniture will break this up with some nice wood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/assets/GardenUpgradeV2.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/GardenUpgradeV2_small.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Garden Upgrade v2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/life/2015/06/10/garden-upgrade-live</link>
                <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/life/2015/06/10/garden-upgrade-live</guid>
                <pubDate>2015-06-10T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Can I get a witness</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Waking up this morning, thinking about the difference between “Can I have” and “Can I get” I wondered whether the perceived Americanism of “Can I get” was actually ruder than “Can I have”. Looking at several sites only showed me the rich diversity of the English language and that there were just as many Americans who thought “Can I get” would be rude as there were those who thought it was perfectly fine. A common theme was that “get” implied getting it yourself, whereas “have” implied a request. Certainly in a restaurant or a cafe there may be some ambiguity of what you were requesting was something you could reach physically yourself. However one of the most common scenarios for this debate seems to be the relatively new phenomenon of the coffee shop. One site had this as the most popular comment;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If I were a waiter and somebody said “can I get a coffee”, I would be inclined to say “go ahead” and then just stand there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;If they the customer then asked where the beverage was, I would say: “Oh, I’m sorry; I thought you wanted to get it yourself. Would you like me to get it for you?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite the fact that the responder here is objecting to perceived rudeness with passive aggression, which in itself is rude, it highlighted that my initial inkling was correct. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Technically of course there is no debate. You’re neither “getting” or “having” a coffee, you’re “buying” or “purchasing” a coffee. Neither are you asking for permission; if you have money you’re very unlikely to be denied a request for coffee in a coffee shop in the current economic climate (although &lt;a href=&quot;http://youtu.be/7WRxEY8o3kc&quot;&gt;ordering soup&lt;/a&gt; isn’t always so straightforward). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then it hit me; modern America is filled with choices. It prides itself in customer services. “Can I get…” is a request always likely to be fulfilled. “Can I get a double shot skinny late with vanilla to go?” is something you have been able to get in America for many years now. The same request, not so long ago in Yorkshire, would have mostly been met with “No, you can &lt;strong&gt;have&lt;/strong&gt; a bloody cup of tea and like it…”&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/thoughts/2014/10/24/can-i-get-a-witness</link>
                <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/thoughts/2014/10/24/can-i-get-a-witness</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-10-24T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Sunday is the new Monday</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;Being an Englishman in New Technology, I’m rather used to changing regional settings. As a former serial Linux experimenter it almost became a reflex action I never even thought about. I was always puzzled by the notion of Sunday as the first day of the week, however as I sit here on a Sunday morning doing my &lt;a href=&quot;gtd&quot;&gt;GTD&lt;/a&gt; weekly review and looking at the week ahead in my calendar it suddenly occurred to me that if I set Sunday as the first day, then when I look at the weekly view in the calendar then I won’t have to move it forward a week. A small thing, granted, but it makes me wonder if that indeed is the reason that America views Sunday as the first day of the week; a desire for progress and looking forward to the future? And so a day of distracted Wikipedia surfing begins…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/technology/2014/10/05/sunday-is-the-new-monday</link>
                <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/technology/2014/10/05/sunday-is-the-new-monday</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-10-05T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Customer Loyalty</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;I got an email from BT who provide my phone and internet about renewing my contract. Now currently my phone isn&#39;t even plugged in, but that&#39;s another story, so I don&#39;t really like having to pay line rental as it is but it seems to be perfectly legal for companies to bundle this in as a requirement. They were asking if I wanted to renew my contract with them, with what initially seemed a worse deal for the same price. I actually took screenshots of the link because I thought the poor person I would end up talking to would be oblivious to this mistake. By the time I actually investigated my contract end date (via a charming lady with a very Indian name who I won&#39;t make any presumptions about where she actually worked) they had corrected this mistake, but sure enough after being a loyal customer for 12 months I was being offered the princely reduction of … £0.00.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe BT weren&#39;t aware they had competitors. Maybe they weren&#39;t aware that those competitors have price reductions for new customers. Maybe they were counting on me being extremely lazy/wealthy/stupid/all of the above. Fortunately for me only (A) applied, and I was able to search for a better deal from the comfort of my sofa. Which isn&#39;t actually that comfy at the moment, but again I digress. I wasn&#39;t going to Sky after I had left them some years ago and have no desire to pay a fortune for things I never watch. I wasn&#39;t going anywhere near Talk Talk as I have only heard complaints about them and nothing positive at all. However I had heard good things about &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.plus.net&quot;&gt;PlusNet&lt;/a&gt; who did fibre. I had fibre with BT being one of the lucky people who can get this service and wasn&#39;t about to give it up with a household rammed full of online gadgets. I checked out the PlusNet cost in a trusty old &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.apple.com/mac/numbers/&quot;&gt;Numbers&lt;/a&gt; spreadsheet and found that I could save just over £16 a month by switching to PlusNet. For the first six months I also got an extra £11 per month off. The only downside is that from what I could tell from online reviews is that the router wasn&#39;t great; well with the initial six month saving I could easily get a better router, and one that supports &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dd-wrt.com&quot;&gt;DD-WRT&lt;/a&gt; which I had always wanted to try out anyway. So, I signed up to PlusNet and asked BT for a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.maccode.org.uk&quot;&gt;MAC code&lt;/a&gt;. I got an email from BT, which I will quote below;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;I&#39;ve looked at your BT account and I can see that youre a loyal and longstanding BT customer and wed really like you to stay with us.&lt;/p&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;For this reason I can reduce your broadband package price from £27.67 per month down to £19.65 per month. This is a fantastic saving of £96.24 over the next 12 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well why on earth wasn&#39;t I offered this in the first place? By trying to save £96.24 in that first instance, it has ended up costing BT £427.68 for the year in lost business. I can only presume that someone has crunched the numbers on renewals and retentions and that I&#39;m in the moinority. I&#39;ve always been happy with the BT Service and had no problems at all with my internet and I may rue switching but the PlusNet contract is 18 months after which of course as a new customer I&#39;ll be welcomed back with all the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bt.com/packages&quot;&gt;latest deals&lt;/a&gt;…&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/customerservice/2014/10/03/customer-loyalty</link>
                <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/customerservice/2014/10/03/customer-loyalty</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-10-03T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
        </item>

        <item>
                <title>Spanking is ok</title>
                <description>
&lt;p&gt;The writer of &lt;a href=&quot;http://thegazette.com/subject/news/nation/for-most-americans-spanking-is-ok-implements-are-not-20141001&quot;&gt;this headline&lt;/a&gt; is either very naive or acutely aware. I&#39;m not entirely sure…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/2014-10-02_spanking.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;spanking&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
                <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/funny/2014/10/02/spanking-headline</link>
                <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/funny/2014/10/02/spanking-headline</guid>
                <pubDate>2014-10-02T00:00:00+01:00</pubDate>
        </item>


</channel>
</rss>
