<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home improvement on Luke Brunning</title>
    <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/home-improvement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home improvement on Luke Brunning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/home-improvement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade Finished</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-07-20-garden-upgrade-finished/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-07-20-garden-upgrade-finished/</guid>
      <description>It had been a long journey since the beginning of spring 2015 realizing that the planned kitchen upgrade was going to have to go on hold in order to fix the garden, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier with the end result. I&amp;rsquo;d had to tone down my plans of what I originally envisaged and was a little worried that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be happy with the end results. None of this would have been possible without Andy Hobson who I was really lucky to find.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade LIVE</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-10-garden-upgrade-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-10-garden-upgrade-live/</guid>
      <description>My garden project is now fully underway! After weeks of trying to find someone to actually work on this project I finally found just the right person. We decided it was best that I project manage the whole thing and he just supply labour as I wanted to specify most of the materials. This has worked out really well. He&amp;apos;s advised me when I needed it and come up with some good ideas of areas which I wasn&amp;apos;t sure about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-06-28-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-06-28-garden/</guid>
      <description>I am looking to upgrade my garden as it is currently in rather a sorry state, as evidenced below (click on the picture for a larger view);

The decking is rotting and is totally impractical in winter. The area above which is decked is to be replaced by Areas A, B and C shown below (click on the picture for a larger view);

 Area A is a small decking area in Thermowood Area B is artifical grass; A Touch of Grass&amp;apos;s &amp;lsquo;El Classico&amp;rsquo; Area C is paved in Indian Stone  The area at the front is out of scope for this project but I will ultimately get this paved in Indian Stone as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>