<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Luke Brunning</title>
    <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Luke Brunning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PS4 Founding Family Patch</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-06-19-ps4-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-06-19-ps4-patch/</guid>
      <description>I came up with an idea for a &amp;lsquo;patch&amp;rsquo; for the PS4 Founding Family group for Elite Dangerous. I found a link on the official Frontier Forums that described how to create a logo from a patch. This is incredibley detailed and well written but this guy is obviously super talented and I got nowhere near in designing the idea I had. I watched a few videos on Lynda.com and I think given enough time I could have come up with something that wasn&amp;rsquo;t totally awful but time was against me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous and Griefing</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-griefing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-griefing/</guid>
      <description>Despite not even being able to play the game Elite Dangerous I find myself preoccupied thinking and discussing it on the internet, primarily in the official Frontier Forums. The word &amp;lsquo;griefing&amp;rsquo; is bandied around a lot by people there and like many words it means different things to different people. I looked to Wikipedia for a definition, but it was a little vague for me. I read the paper which was referenced in the article and being an academic paper it was a little more detailed and I now accept this definition as my working one;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My PSN Name</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-psn-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-psn-name/</guid>
      <description>I bought my Playstation 4 Pro on Black Friday, 2016. I had been a XBox 360 player for about the last ten years or so, and for various reasons decided to switch teams. I&amp;rsquo;d never played online on the 360 and never really envisaged playing online with the PS4. So when it arrived and I signed up online I just jumped in with my real name, not thinking it would ever be an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous on PlayStation®4 FAQ</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-24-ed-ps4-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-24-ed-ps4-faq/</guid>
      <description>After wondering how Frontier&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;disconcertingly vague&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Nothing to announce at this time&amp;rdquo; actually pan out over time I thought I would make a note of their current FAQs for PS4 here and keep an eye on developments after it was announced on several websites today that there would be a physical disc copy of ED released for PS4 and XBox One. The update date below is Frontier&amp;rsquo;s, not mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-22-elite-dangerous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-22-elite-dangerous/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m tremendously excited by Elite Dangerous making an appearance on Playstation 4. I spent many happy hours as a child playing the original Elite on my Acorn Electron in the 80s. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember exactly what rank I managed to get up to but it certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t Elite. The originality and advanced nature is a matter of record now but what really hooked me was that ever since seeing Star Wars at the age of four I had spent most of my formative years wishing to be whisked away into space on a spaceship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Tools are Not Toys</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-03-08-your-tools-are-not-toys/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-03-08-your-tools-are-not-toys/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately my beloved TextExpander has recently stopped working in ConEmu. Ironically this coincided with the update notes proudly declaring that expansion was now working in ConEmu! Those nice people at Smile are helping me get to the bottom of it, but in the mean time I decided to look around at the options in the console world in Windows. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to take long.
I opened up the PowerShell ISE; I&amp;rsquo;ve never really used it, preferring Sublime Text (I&amp;rsquo;ve also been flirting with Visual Studio Code) but I grabbed a Solarized theme and thought it may be fun to the &amp;lsquo;Intellisense&amp;rsquo; available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade Finished</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-07-20-garden-upgrade-finished/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-07-20-garden-upgrade-finished/</guid>
      <description>It had been a long journey since the beginning of spring 2015 realizing that the planned kitchen upgrade was going to have to go on hold in order to fix the garden, but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t be happier with the end result. I&amp;rsquo;d had to tone down my plans of what I originally envisaged and was a little worried that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be happy with the end results. None of this would have been possible without Andy Hobson who I was really lucky to find.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Today’s Earworm</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-28-todays-earworm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-28-todays-earworm/</guid>
      <description>Today&amp;rsquo;s earworm is brought to you by Fairport Convention;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade LIVE</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-10-garden-upgrade-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2015-06-10-garden-upgrade-live/</guid>
      <description>My garden project is now fully underway! After weeks of trying to find someone to actually work on this project I finally found just the right person. We decided it was best that I project manage the whole thing and he just supply labour as I wanted to specify most of the materials. This has worked out really well. He&amp;apos;s advised me when I needed it and come up with some good ideas of areas which I wasn&amp;apos;t sure about.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Can I get a witness</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-24-can-i-get-a-witness/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-24-can-i-get-a-witness/</guid>
      <description>Waking up this morning, thinking about the difference between &amp;ldquo;Can I have&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Can I get&amp;rdquo; I wondered whether the perceived Americanism of &amp;ldquo;Can I get&amp;rdquo; was actually ruder than &amp;ldquo;Can I have&amp;rdquo;. Looking at several sites only showed me the rich diversity of the English language and that there were just as many Americans who thought &amp;ldquo;Can I get&amp;rdquo; would be rude as there were those who thought it was perfectly fine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sunday is the new Monday</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-05-sunday-is-the-new-monday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-05-sunday-is-the-new-monday/</guid>
      <description>Being an Englishman in New Technology, I&amp;rsquo;m rather used to changing regional settings. As a former serial Linux experimenter it almost became a reflex action I never even thought about. I was always puzzled by the notion of Sunday as the first day of the week, however as I sit here on a Sunday morning doing my GTD weekly review and looking at the week ahead in my calendar it suddenly occurred to me that if I set Sunday as the first day, then when I look at the weekly view in the calendar then I won&amp;rsquo;t have to move it forward a week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Loyalty</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-03-customer-loyalty/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-03-customer-loyalty/</guid>
      <description>I got an email from BT who provide my phone and internet about renewing my contract. Now currently my phone isn&amp;apos;t even plugged in, but that&amp;apos;s another story, so I don&amp;apos;t really like having to pay line rental as it is but it seems to be perfectly legal for companies to bundle this in as a requirement. They were asking if I wanted to renew my contract with them, with what initially seemed a worse deal for the same price.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spanking is ok</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-02-spanking-headline/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-10-02-spanking-headline/</guid>
      <description>The writer of this headline is either very naive or acutely aware. I&amp;apos;m not entirely sure&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden Upgrade</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-06-28-garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2014-06-28-garden/</guid>
      <description>I am looking to upgrade my garden as it is currently in rather a sorry state, as evidenced below (click on the picture for a larger view);

The decking is rotting and is totally impractical in winter. The area above which is decked is to be replaced by Areas A, B and C shown below (click on the picture for a larger view);

 Area A is a small decking area in Thermowood Area B is artifical grass; A Touch of Grass&amp;apos;s &amp;lsquo;El Classico&amp;rsquo; Area C is paved in Indian Stone  The area at the front is out of scope for this project but I will ultimately get this paved in Indian Stone as well.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>