<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on Luke Brunning</title>
    <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on Luke Brunning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/categories/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous HOTAS on the PS4</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-07-11-ed-hotas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-07-11-ed-hotas/</guid>
      <description>I want to preface this post with the caveat that the HOTAS seems to be a very devisive device (see what I did there?) and if you can purchase one where you can return it then that is by far the best option.
I&amp;rsquo;m not going to address other people&amp;rsquo;s criticism of the stick because they are valid enough, but for me it came down to the things I liked about it being more important that those that I didn&amp;rsquo;t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PS4 Founding Family Patch</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-06-19-ps4-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-06-19-ps4-patch/</guid>
      <description>I came up with an idea for a &amp;lsquo;patch&amp;rsquo; for the PS4 Founding Family group for Elite Dangerous. I found a link on the official Frontier Forums that described how to create a logo from a patch. This is incredibley detailed and well written but this guy is obviously super talented and I got nowhere near in designing the idea I had. I watched a few videos on Lynda.com and I think given enough time I could have come up with something that wasn&amp;rsquo;t totally awful but time was against me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous and Griefing</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-griefing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-griefing/</guid>
      <description>Despite not even being able to play the game Elite Dangerous I find myself preoccupied thinking and discussing it on the internet, primarily in the official Frontier Forums. The word &amp;lsquo;griefing&amp;rsquo; is bandied around a lot by people there and like many words it means different things to different people. I looked to Wikipedia for a definition, but it was a little vague for me. I read the paper which was referenced in the article and being an academic paper it was a little more detailed and I now accept this definition as my working one;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My PSN Name</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-psn-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-05-03-psn-name/</guid>
      <description>I bought my Playstation 4 Pro on Black Friday, 2016. I had been a XBox 360 player for about the last ten years or so, and for various reasons decided to switch teams. I&amp;rsquo;d never played online on the 360 and never really envisaged playing online with the PS4. So when it arrived and I signed up online I just jumped in with my real name, not thinking it would ever be an issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous on PlayStation®4 FAQ</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-24-ed-ps4-faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-24-ed-ps4-faq/</guid>
      <description>After wondering how Frontier&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;disconcertingly vague&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Nothing to announce at this time&amp;rdquo; actually pan out over time I thought I would make a note of their current FAQs for PS4 here and keep an eye on developments after it was announced on several websites today that there would be a physical disc copy of ED released for PS4 and XBox One. The update date below is Frontier&amp;rsquo;s, not mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elite Dangerous</title>
      <link>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-22-elite-dangerous/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lukebrunning.co.uk/blog/2017-04-22-elite-dangerous/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m tremendously excited by Elite Dangerous making an appearance on Playstation 4. I spent many happy hours as a child playing the original Elite on my Acorn Electron in the 80s. I can&amp;rsquo;t remember exactly what rank I managed to get up to but it certainly wasn&amp;rsquo;t Elite. The originality and advanced nature is a matter of record now but what really hooked me was that ever since seeing Star Wars at the age of four I had spent most of my formative years wishing to be whisked away into space on a spaceship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>